oh for starting the video
It was going to be really nice,
I'm falling like this,
right?
here or
haha
is bum
bonzão Maravilha
we guy brought the boxes see yeah
when is this fair going to be
Saturday and Sunday there at the square
whore old fair
well we'll take it there later I'll explain there
cool this is what I wanted to show you
I call you from my brother
and i wanted to put this on for us
when we go marketing
some noise suddenly we use it on
type put in the event at this fair bro
it's then that you think skateboarding here was from crying
brother caraca
what is the energy like
i'm already feeling it now i'm going to start giving ollie
it already looks like him here too it looks like it does
what an honor to give 1 roll with skateboard Weeping guy bro
valeu valeu
calm there
oh look there bro
Charlie Brown
1 more there now o
but 1 Ali bro
still there we there bro
is picking up
good night let's go to the next one
oh there we there bro
caraca brother Charlie Brown
tamo together
valeu as mine ends up meeting
the brand
the cap
the car has the author and this is one of the strategies
that i'm trying to strengthen
more and more here in the city of Santos
it's on let's go bro
nah
udah
go